{
    "yes": [
        {
            "question": "When did the International Court of Justice begin its work?",
            "answer": "April 1946",
            "reformulated_question": "Did the International Court of Justice begin its work in April 1946?",
            "reformulated_answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who portrays the character of Daniel LaRusso in the Karate Kid film series?",
            "answer": "Ralph Macchio",
            "reformulated_question": "Is it Ralph Macchio who portrays the character of Daniel LaRusso in the Karate Kid film series?",
            "reformulated_answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who founded Westinghouse Electric Corporation?",
            "answer": "George Westinghouse",
            "reformulated_question": "Was it George Westinghouse who founded Westinghouse Electric Corporation?",
            "reformulated_answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "In which country are Bonobos exclusively found?",
            "answer": "Democratic Republic of Congo",
            "reformulated_question": "Is it in Democratic Republic of Congo that are Bonobos exclusively found?",
            "reformulated_answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "In what year did the Persian Empire, also known as the Achaemenid Empire, come into existence?",
            "answer": "550 BCE",
            "reformulated_question": "Was it in 550 BCE that did the Persian Empire, also known as the Achaemenid Empire, come into existence?",
            "reformulated_answer": "Yes"
        }
    ],
    "no": [
        {
            "question": "What is the real name of the lead singer of Guns N' Roses, commonly known as Axl Rose?",
            "answer": "William Bruce Rose Jr",
            "reformulated_question": "Is William Jack Rosy the real name of the lead singer of Guns N' Roses, commonly known as Axl Rose?",
            "reformulated_answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the co-creator of Mickey Mouse alongside Walt Disney?",
            "answer": "Ub Iwerks",
            "reformulated_question": "Was Josephy Disney the co-creator of Mickey Mouse alongside Walt Disney?",
            "reformulated_answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "What company merged with Lockheed Corporation in March 1995 to form Lockheed Martin?",
            "answer": "Martin Marietta",
            "reformulated_question": "Is Google the company that merged with Lockheed Corporation in March 1995 to form Lockheed Martin?",
            "reformulated_answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "When was Will Jennings born?",
            "answer": "June 27 1944",
            "reformulated_question": "Was Will Jennings born in June 27 1945?",
            "reformulated_answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the real name of the lead singer of Guns N' Roses, commonly known as Axl Rose?",
            "answer": "William Bruce Rose Jr",
            "reformulated_question": "Does Apple Music co-owns Syco Entertainment along with Simon Cowell, the parent company of Syco Music?",
            "reformulated_answer": "No"
        }
    ]
}